Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1932-2004; XVIII.
  - Attorney General of the United States, 1988-1991; 11.
    - Events and People
      - National Council of Jewish Women--DOJ Session (3), March 13, 1989 (Box 1533, Folder 33)
      - National Crime Prevention Council with McGruff (8), December 6, 1989 (Box 1533, Folder 34)
      - National Crime Victims Ceremony, Rose Garden (9), April 25, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 35)
      - National District Attorneys Association Executive Committee (1), May 5, 1989 (Box 1533, Folder 36)
      - National Governors' Association--Winter Meeting (6), February 27, 1989 (Box 1533, Folder 37)
      - National Board of Corrections, Advisory Board Members (3), September 16, 1988 (Box 1533, Folder 38)
      - National Law Enforcement Council (2), September 12, 1988 (Box 1533, Folder 39)
      - National Law Enforcement Officers Memorial--DOJ Exhibit (1), December 12, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 40)
      - National Organization of Black Law Enforcement Executives (NOBLE) (1), February 27, 1989 (Box 1533, Folder 41)
      - National Sheriff's Association, Denver, CO (1), June 26, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 42)
      - Navarro, Bruce and Philip (1), June 1, 1990 (Box 1533, Folder 43)
      - Neptue, Jill, IOP (1), October 5, 1989 (Box 1533, Folder 44)
      - Office Photographs, including Thornburgh with Lincoln Bust (August 23, 1988), 1981-1988 (Box 1533, Folder 45)
      - Office of the Attorney General--200th Anniversary Party (9), September 22, 1989 (Box 1534, Folder 1)
      - Office of the Attorney General Scheduling Staff (2), May 7, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 2)
      - Office of Intelligence Policy and Review--Brown Bag Lunch (2), February 15, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 3)
      - Office of Intelligence Policy and Review--Brown Bag Lunch (2), February 20, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 4)
      - Office of Justice Programs--Brown Bag Lunch (3), December 20, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 5)
      - Office of Legal Council--Brown Bag Lunch (14), October 19, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 6)
      - Office of Legislative Affairs--Brown Bag Lunch (2), April 9, 1991 (Box 1534, Folder 7)
      - Office of Liaison Services--Brown Bag Lunch (2), April 11, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 8)
      - Office of Liaison Services (1), February 17, 1989 (Box 1534, Folder 9)
      - Office of Policy Development (15), February 2, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 10)
      - Oncken, Henry, USA from Southern District of TX (1), undated (Box 1534, Folder 11)
      - Organized Crime Council Meeting (2), January 17, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 12)
      - Palmer, Jim (1), June, 1991 (Box 1534, Folder 13)
      - Parr, John, President of National Civic League (1), undated (Box 1534, Folder 14)
      - Payne v. Tennessee Amicus Agreement (7), April 24, 1991 (Box 1534, Folder 15)
      - Pennsylvania American Legion Convention, Pittsburgh, PA (1), July 13, 1989 (Box 1534, Folder 16)
      - Pennsylvania Restaurant Association (2), September 25, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 17)
      - Pepperdine University School of Law Dinner (5), February 2, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 18)
      - Philadelphia Bar Association (6), September 30, 1988 (Box 1534, Folder 19)
      - Pike Institute for the Handicapped--Boston University (12), September 14, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 20)
      - Pittsburgh Penguins--Presidential Salute (5), June 24, 1991 (Box 1534, Folder 21)
      - Poppler, Doris, U.S. Attorney from Billings, MT (1), September 20, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 22)
      - Powell, LTG Colin (2), July 6, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 23)
      - Presbyterian Church National Leaders (2), May 3, 1989 (Box 1534, Folder 24)
      - President Bush's Address to U. S. Attorneys Financial Institution Fraud Conference (8), June 22, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 25)
      - President Bush's "A Salute to Public Services", January 26, 1989 (Box 1534, Folder 26)
      - Presidential Exchange Executives (1), March 29, 1991 (Box 1534, Folder 27)
      - Presidential Rank Awards (12), November 1, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 28)
      - Procurement Fraud Conference (6), May 21, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 29)
      - QUAD Squad/Tampa--Pinellas County, FL (4), May 31, 1991 (Box 1534, Folder 30)
      - Quayle, Dan and Marilyn (7), 1988-1991 (Box 1534, Folder 31)
      - Quayle, Vice President Dan--Luncheon (5), December 19, 1989 (Box 1534, Folder 32)
      - Raven, Robert, President ABA (1), March 15, 1989 (Box 1534, Folder 33)
      - Reagan, President--Domestic Policy Farewell Speech (3), December 13, 1988 (Box 1534, Folder 34)
      - Reagan, President--Meeting in the Oval Office (1), October 6, 1988 (Box 1534, Folder 35)
      - Regula, Congressman Ralph (2), October 18, 1988 (Box 1534, Folder 36)
      - July 13, 1989 (Box 1534, Folder 37)
      - Rivera-Cruz, Hector, Puerto Rico Justice Minister (2), March 7, 1991 (Box 1534, Folder 38)
      - Robinson, Michael of Public Affairs (1), April 4, 1991 (Box 1534, Folder 39)
      - Romano, Benito, USA of Southern District of NY and Louie Freeh (3), undated (Box 1534, Folder 40)
      - Rosenberg, Chuck (1), October 11, 1990 (Box 1534, Folder 41)
      - Rosenberg, Harry, U.S. Attorney from New Orleans, LA (1), February 23, 1991 (Box 1534, Folder 42)
      - Sakely, Mark, OPD and Bill Mercer, OPD (1), August 5, 1991 (Box 1535, Folder 1)
      - Schall, Tony, Office of Attorney General and Family (1), June 12, 1991 (Box 1535, Folder 2)
      - Schedule "C" Reception (3), March 27, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 3)
      - Schuyler, Thom (1), undated (Box 1535, Folder 4)
      - Schwartz, Linda (1), undated (Box 1535, Folder 5)
      - Senior Executive Association Reception (1), November 1, 1988 (Box 1535, Folder 6)
      - Senior Interagency Group on Financial Institution Fraud (1), July 31, 1991 (Box 1535, Folder 7)
      - Session, William, Director of the FBI (3), November 2, 1988 (Box 1535, Folder 8)
      - Shapiro, Dan (2), undated (Box 1535, Folder 9)
      - Sheehy, Bob, Special Agent (2), April 24, 1991 (Box 1535, Folder 10)
      - Short, Duke, RISS (2), May 23, 1989 (Box 1535, Folder 11)
      - Shur, Gerald, Criminal Division (1), May 17, 1991 (Box 1535, Folder 12)
      - Simmons, R. P., Chairman of Executive Committee of the Specialty Steel Industry (3), June 22, 1989 (Box 1535, Folder 13)
      - Smitanka, John, Grand Rapids, MI (1), undated (Box 1535, Folder 14)
      - Smith, Don, LAPD (1), February 5, 1991 (Box 1535, Folder 15)
      - Smith, Karen, Office of Attorney General (1), undated (Box 1535, Folder 16)
      - Smith, Peg (1), undated (Box 1535, Folder 17)
      - Sofaer, Judge Abraham, State Department Legal Advisor (1), May 25, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 18)
      - Solicitor General Centennial Commemorating William Howard Taft's Appointment (7), February 22, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 19)
      - Starek, Millie (1), October 11, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 20)
      - Starr, Ken, Solicitor General Reception (1), July 28, 1989 (Box 1535, Folder 21)
      - State Attorneys General--Meeting (1), undated (Box 1535, Folder 22)
      - State Bar Presidents--DOJ Briefing (6), October 26, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 23)
      - State Justice Institute (2), November 30, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 24)
      - Stratton, Hal, AG of New Mexico (1), June 12, 1989 (Box 1535, Folder 25)
      - Studeman, Vice Admiral William, Director of National Security Agency (1), undated (Box 1535, Folder 26)
      - Suarez, Xavier, Mayor of Miami (1), August 3, 1989 (Box 1535, Folder 27)
      - Supreme Court and Cabinet at Camp David (1), April 20, 1991 (Box 1535, Folder 28)
      - Supreme Court, Opening Session (6), October 3, 1988 (Box 1535, Folder 29)
      - Sweet Bob, Director of the Office of Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Program (1), April 12, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 30)
      - Tabor, John and Kate (1), April 12, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 31)
      - Taranto, Richard G. (1), undated (Box 1535, Folder 32)
      - Tax Division Executives--Brown Bag Lunch (3), April 3, 1991 (Box 1535, Folder 33)
      - Tax Division 1991 Summer Interns (2), July 12, 1991 (Box 1535, Folder 34)
      - Team 100--White House Dinner (1), undated (Box 1535, Folder 35)
      - Thomas, Judge Clarence--Swearing In Ceremony (5), April 30, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 36)
      - Thornburgh, Ann and Margi Hurlburt--Drop-By Visit (2), March 20, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 37)
      - Thornburgh, Virginia and Friends (1), February 9, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 38)
      - Thornburgh, Virginia, Speaking, 1989 (Box 1535, Folder 39)
      - U.S. Conference of Mayors (1), February 26, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 40)
      - U.S. Marine Corps--Sunset Parade (1), June 18, 1991 (Box 1535, Folder 41)
      - U.S. Marshals Service--Bicentennial Exhibit Tour at the Supreme Court (5), October 18, 1988 (Box 1535, Folder 42)
      - U.S. Parole Commission (3), March 28, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 43)
      - U.S. Trustees Conference (1), June 26, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 44)
      - University of Puget Sound Law School (14), March 21, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 45)
      - Urgenson, Larry, Fraud Section Chief (1), January 30, 1990 (Box 1535, Folder 46)
      - Virginia Summit on Drugs Reception and Banquet (10), April 16, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 1)
      - Von Colditz, John, Friend of Ann Thornburgh (2), November 17, 1988\ (Box 1536, Folder 2)
      - Watkins, Admiral Bill (1), undated (Box 1536, Folder 3)
      - Wayes, Charles, 1988 Principal of the Year (1), undated (Box 1536, Folder 4)
      - Weis, Judge Joseph, Jr., Chairman of Federal Court Study Commission (2), April 2, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 5)
      - West, James J., U.S. Attorney for Middle District of Pennsylvania (1), September 27, ? (Box 1536, Folder 6)
      - Weyrich, Paul, Free Congress Foundation (3), May 24, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 7)
      - White House Correspondents' Dinner (1), April 28, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 8)
      - Whitley, Joe, ODAG--Farewell Reception (2), June 21, 1989 (Box 1536, Folder 9)
      - Wiesenthal, Simon (3), April 26, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 10)
      - Wilburn, Robert, President of the Carnegie (2), April 16, 1991 (Box 1536, Folder 11)
      - Wilder, Douglas (2), February 26, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 12)
      - Woodward, Pat (1), May 18, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 13)
      - World Affairs Council throughout the World (2), October 1, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 14)
      - Yale, Ken, DPC Executive Secretary (1), September 11, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 15)
      - Yale Political Union (3), March 13, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 16)
      - Yob, Charles (1), September 14, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 17)
      - Young American Medal Awards (17), September 21, 1989 (Box 1536, Folder 18)
      - Young American Medal Awards (3), November 13, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 19)
    - Congressional Photographs
      - Asian-American Student Quotas--Meeting with Gingrich, Hunter, Rohrabacher, and Saiki (1), July 18, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 20)
      - Bartlett, Congressman Steve (1), December 17, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 21)
      - Chaffee, Senator John and Congressman Ron Machtley (2), July 11, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 22)
      - Conte, Congressman Silvio and Hal Rogers, Justice Appropriations (2), September 18, 1989 (Box 1536, Folder 23)
      - Dornan, Congressman John (1), May 23, 1989 (Box 1536, Folder 24)
      - Fair Housing Bill Signing Ceremony, White House (1), September 13, 1988 (Box 1536, Folder 25)
      - Gorton, Senator Slade and Michael McGavick (1), January 15, 1991 (Box 1536, Folder 26)
      - Hatch, Senator Orrin (1), July 24, 1991 (Box 1536, Folder 27)
      - Heflin, Senator Howell and Winston Lett, Chief Counsel (1), November 15, 1989 (Box 1536, Folder 28)
      - House Appropriations Subcommittee Meeting (6), February 28, 1989 (Box 1536, Folder 29)
      - Lugar, Senator Richard (1), May 10, 1991 (Box 1536, Folder 30)
      - McCollum, Congressman Bill--Crime Package Press Conference (3), September 26, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 31)
      - Senate Judiciary Hearing (2), August 5, 1988 (Box 1536, Folder 32)
      - Senate Testimony on Strike Forces (3), September 8, 1989 (Box 1536, Folder 33)
      - Senate Labor and Human Resources Committee on Americans with Disabilities Act (8), June 22, 1989 (Box 1536, Folder 34)
      - Seymour, Senator John (2), January 16, 1991 (Box 1536, Folder 35)
      - Smith, Congressman Neal and George Schafer (1), March 6, 1991 (Box 1536, Folder 36)
      - Stevens, Senator Ted (1), April 26, 1991 (Box 1536, Folder 37)
      - Thurmond, Senator Strom (2), October 25, 1989 (Box 1536, Folder 38)
      - Warner, Senator John (2), January 19, 1990 (Box 1536, Folder 39)
      - Wylie, Congressman Chalmers (1), January 10, 1991 (Box 1536, Folder 40)
    - International Photographs
      - Ajibola, Prince Bola, Attorney General of Nigeria (5), September 12, 1989 (Box 1537, Folder 1)
      - Alvarez, Enrique, Attorney General of Mexico (3), April 14, 1989 (Box 1537, Folder 2)
      - Andreani, Jacques, French Ambassador to the U.S. (2), February 23, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 3)
      - Arad, Moshe H.E., Ambassador of Israel (1), October 11, 1988 (Box 1537, Folder 4)
      - Arias, Oscar, President of Costa Rica (9), April 4, 1989 (Box 1537, Folder 5)
      - Arias Calderon, Ricardo, First Vice President and Justice Minister of Panama (4), November 29, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 6)
      - Babiuc, Victor, Justice Minister of Romania (2), June 20, 1991 (Box 1537, Folder 7)
      - Barrett, David and Steve Butland, Canadian Members of Parliament (1), May 15, 1991 (Box 1537, Folder 8)
      - Boesterud, Helen Marie, Minister of Justice of Norway (1), March 27, 1989 (Box 1537, Folder 9)
      - Bowen, Lionel, Deputy Prime Minister and AG of Australia (5), September 18, 1989 (Box 1537, Folder 10)
      - Briggs, Everett, U.S. Ambassador to Portugal (1), March 30, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 11)
      - Brittan, Sir Leon, Vice President of the European Communities Commission (2), January 15, 1991 (Box 1537, Folder 12)
      - Burney, Derek, Canadian Ambassador and Edouard Brunner, Swiss Ambassador (3), September 21, 1989 (Box 1537, Folder 13)
      - Busby, Morris, Ambassador at Large for Counter-Terrorism (1), January 15, 1991 (Box 1537, Folder 14)
      - Campbell, Kim, Canadian Minister of Justice (3), April 18, 1991 (Box 1537, Folder 15)
      - Attorney General's Trip to Canada (13), October 17, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 16)
      - Carillo Olea, General Jorge, General Coordinator for Investigation and Combat of Drug Trafficking for the Republic of Mexico (5), January 22, 1991 (Box 1537, Folder 17)
      - Carpizo, Dr. Jorge, Mexican Commission on Human Rights (3), April 15, 1991 (Box 1537, Folder 18)
      - Catto, Henry E., Ambassador to the United Kingdom (1), April 7, 1989 (Box 1537, Folder 19)
      - Cocuera, Jose Luis, Minister of the Interior of Spain (8), March 2, 1989 (Box 1537, Folder 20)
      - Cordoba, Dr. Jose, Chief Advisor to the President of Mexico (2), November 14, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 21)
      - Cruz, Rogelio, Attorney General of Panama (4), July 25, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 22)
      - Delius, Carlos, Bolivian Ambassador to the U.S. (1), undated (Box 1537, Folder 23)
      - Diplomatic Corps Dinner (1), February 1, 1989 (Box 1537, Folder 24)
      - Dubinin, Bladimiovich Yuiry, Soviet Ambassador to the U.S. (1), May 18, 1989 (Box 1537, Folder 25)
      - Einaudi, Luigi, U.S. Ambassador to the OAS and Mel Levitsky, Assistant Secretary of State (2), April 16, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 26)
      - Endara, Guillermo, President of Panama (2), April 30, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 27)
      - Evans, Gareth, Australian Minister of Foreign Affairs and Trade (4), October 8, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 28)
      - Ford, Guillermo, Vice President of Thailand (8), March 24, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 29)
      - Ford, Guillermo, Vice President of Thailand (4), March 26, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 30)
      - Franco-American Judicial Exchange Luncheon (5), September 7, 1989 (Box 1537, Folder 31)
      - Fraser, Lord Advocate of Scotland (1), January 24, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 32)
      - Freivalds, Laila, Swedish Minister of Justice (6), April 2, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 33)
      - Gava, Antonio, Italian Minister of the Interior (13), April 4, 1989 (Box 1537, Folder 34)
      - Gaviria, Cesar, President of Colombia (7), September 28, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 35)
      - Gaviria, Cesar, President of Colombia (8), February 26, 1990 (Box 1537, Folder 36)
      - Gelb, Bruce, U.S. Ambassador to Belgium (2), June 21, 1991 (Box 1537, Folder 37)
      - Giraldo Angel, Jaime, Colombian Minister of Justice and Carlos Arrieta, Attorney General of Colombia (4), February 26, 1991 (Box 1538, Folder 1)
      - Godhino, Minister Jose Silveir, Portugal (1), August 22, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 2)
      - Guatemala Trip (10), January, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 3)
      - Guatemalan Judges Meeting (3), undated (Box 1538, Folder 4)
      - Han, Xu, Ambassador of China (1), May 3, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 5)
      - Hecht, Chic, Ambassador-Designate to the Bahamas (1), May 30, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 6)
      - Hocke, Jean Pierre, Commissioner of the United Nations for Refugees (1), June 6, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 7)
      - Hogg, Douglas Honorable, British Undersecretary for Home Affairs (3), May 25, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 8)
      - Horyn, Mykhailo, Popular Movement of the Ukraine (2), September 11, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 9)
      - Huffington, Roy, U.S. Ambassador to Austria (2), April 16, 1991 (Box 1538, Folder 10)
      - Hyun, Hong-Choo, Korean Ambassador to the U.S. (3), June 24, 1991 (Box 1538, Folder 11)
      - Jacobi, Klaus, Ambassador of Switzerland, Mark Richard, and Kurt Hochner (1), November 16, 1988 (Box 1538, Folder 12)
      - Japan Trip (11), September, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 13)
      - Johansson, Bengt, Swedish Minister for Public Administration (2), January 7, 1991 (Box 1538, Folder 14)
      - Kolleck, Teddy, Mayor of Jerusalem (2), November 16, 1988 (Box 1538, Folder 15)
      - Korean Trip (9), September, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 16)
      - Kulcsar, Dr. Kalman, Minister of Justice of Hungary (4), March 30, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 17)
      - Lacalle, Luis, President-Elect of Uruguay ( 2), February 4, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 18)
      - Lacalle, Luis, Delegation to Uruguay for Inauguration of (1), March 1, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 19)
      - LaFontant, Jewel, U.S. Ambassador-at-Large and U.S. Coordinator for Refugee Affairs (1), September 11, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 20)
      - Lane, Bill, U.S. Ambassador to Australia (1), February 24, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 21)
      - Lewis, Doug, Attorney General of Canada (3), January 25, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 22)
      - Lintner, Eduard, Parliamentary State Secretary and German Interior Minister (5), April 11, 1991 (Box 1538, Folder 23)
      - Loeschnak, Frank, Austrian Minister of Justice (2), November 29, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 24)
      - London FBI Legatt Office (10), December, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 25)
      - Loudjev, Dimitar, Deputy Prime Minister of Bulgaria (4), July 23, 1991 (Box 1538, Folder 26)
      - Lushchikov, Sergei, Minister of Justice of the USSR (3), February 19, 1991 (Box 1538, Folder 27)
      - MacLean, Roberto, Peruvian Ambassador to the U.S. (1), June 28, 1991 (Box 1538, Folder 28)
      - Majewski, Henryk, Interior Minister of Poland (2), March 22, 1991 (Box 1538, Folder 29)
      - Marchenko, Dr. Mikhail, Dean of Moscow State University Law School (2), February 14, 1991 (Box 1538, Folder 30)
      - Mayhew, Patrick, Attorney General of the United Kingdom (1), June 26, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 31)
      - Medina, Gustava, Attorney General of Ecuador (2), June 19, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 32)
      - Melady, Thomas, U.S. Ambassador to the Holy See (2), May 29, 1991 (Box 1538, Folder 33)
      - Meridor, Dan, Justice Minister of Israel (1), June 16, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 34)
      - Mexico-Monterey Trip (2), November, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 35)
      - Moore, Ambassador Jonathan, U.S. Ambassador of Refugee Affairs Coordinator (1), undated (Box 1538, Folder 36)
      - Moore, Richard, Ambassador to Ireland (3), July 28, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 37)
      - Mugica, Enrique, Spanish Minister of Justice (4), October 15, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 38)
      - Murata, Ryohei, Ambassador of Japan (2), April 12, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 39)
      - Murray, John, Attorney General of Ireland (2), undated (Box 1538, Folder 40)
      - McWeeney, Sean, Attorney General of the Bahamas (2), February 9, 1990 (Box 1538, Folder 41)
      - Ndinga-Oba, Antoine, Minister of Foreign Affairs of the Congo and Ambassador Martin Adouki, Congolese Permanent U.N. Representative (1), October 10, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 42)
      - Negroponte, John, Ambassador to Mexico (2), June 22, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 43)
      - Ney, Edward, Ambassador-Designate to Canada (1), June 14, 1989 (Box 1538, Folder 44)
      - Orlov, Vladimir, Soviet Central Election Committee (3), November 8, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 1)
      - Ortega, Temistocles, Columbian Vice Minister of Justice (2), March 17, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 2)
      - Park, Tong-Tin, Ambassador of the Republic of Korea (2), August 21, 1990 (Box 1539, Folder 3)
      - Plazas Alcid, Guillermo, Colombian Minister of Justice (3), undated (Box 1539, Folder 4)
      - Pope John Paul II (11), December 6, 1990 (Box 1539, Folder 5)
      - Quayle, Marilyn, Trip to U.S.S.R. (3), November 8, 1990 (Box 1539, Folder 6)
      - Queen Elizabeth II, State Visit (3), May 14, 1991 (Box 1539, Folder 7)
      - Raiz, Karmella, Soviet Refusenik (2), January 2, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 8)
      - Rattray, Rafael "Carl", Minister of Justice and Attorney General of Jamaica (1), May 19, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 9)
      - Richter, Leon, Czech Minister of Justice (3), June 21, 1991 (Box 1539, Folder 10)
      - Roger, Oscar, Attorney General of Argentina (3), May 1, 1990 (Box 1539, Folder 11)
      - Roskens, Ronald, Agency for International Development (3), March 15, 1991 (Box 1539, Folder 12)
      - Rubinstein, Elyakim, Israeli Cabinet Secretary (1), February 24, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 13)
      - Russia Trip (4), October, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 14)
      - Sanguinetti, Julio Maria, President of Uruguay (1), September 18, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 15)
      - Sassou-Nguesso, Denis, President of the Congo (6), February 14, 1990 (Box 1539, Folder 16)
      - Schifter, Dick, Assistant Secretary of State for Human Rights (1), November 30, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 17)
      - Schnaueuble, Wolfgain, West German Minister of the Interior (3), February 21, 1990 (Box 1539, Folder 18)
      - Scottish Investigators--Pan Am #101 (3), April 9, 1991 (Box 1539, Folder 19)
      - Secchia, Pete, Ambassador to Italy (1), August 23, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 20)
      - Seitz, Raymond, U.S. Ambassador-Designate to the UK (1), April 30, 1991 (Box 1539, Folder 21)
      - Shamir, Yitzhak, Prime Minister of Israel --White House Dinner (1), April 6, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 22)
      - Shamir, Yitzhak, Prime Minister of Israel--Vice President's Luncheon (1), December 12, 1990 (Box 1539, Folder 23)
      - Shimojo, Shin-ichiro, Minister of Health and Welfare in Japan (3), June 25, 1991 (Box 1539, Folder 24)
      - Solana, Fernanco, Mexican Secretary of Foreign Relations (3), March 21, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 25)
      - South American Trip--Press Conference Following the Trip (5), March 8, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 26)
      - Soviet Union Trip, DOJ Legal Expert Meeting (2), October, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 27)
      - Supreme Soviet Delegation (5), November 27, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 28)
      - Tate, Senator Michael, Australian Minister of Justice (3), June 23, 1989 (Box 1539, Folder 29)
      - Torpornin, Boris, Soviet Institute of State and Law (2), March 6, 1990 (Box 1539, Folder 30)
      - United Nations--AG's Remarks before UN Committee on Social, Humanitarian and Cultural Matters, New York, NY (15), November 2, 1990 (Box 1539, Folder 31)